[
    {
        "question": "Which of these is NOT a class in Dungeons & Dragons 5th edition?",
        "answers": [
            "Druid",
            "Magus",
            "Barbarian",
            "Rogue"
        ],
        "correct": 2
    },
    {
        "question": "In what year did Dungeons & Dragons get acquired by Wizards of the Coast?",
        "answers": [
            "1991",
            "1994",
            "1997",
            "2000"
        ],
        "correct": 3
    },
    {
        "question": "Which of these cities is not part of the Faer√ªn?",
        "answers": [
            "Baldur's Gate",
            "Neverwinter",
            "Thultanthar",
            "Sigil"
        ],
        "correct": 4
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the first fictional setting for Dungeons & Dragons?",
        "answers": [
            "Forgotten Realms",
            "Spelljammer",
            "Greyhawk",
            "Blackmoor"
        ],
        "correct": 4
    },
    {
        "question": "In the Forgotten Realms, which of these creatures would be seen as the Handmaidens of Lolth?",
        "answers": [
            "Yugoloth",
            "Yochlol",
            "Drider",
            "Succubi"
        ],
        "correct": 2
    },
    {
        "question": "Which of these deities was destroyed by Helm during the time of Troubles?",
        "answers": [
            "Bhaal",
            "Asmodeus",
            "Mask",
            "Mystra"
        ],
        "correct": 4
    },
    {
        "question": "What school of magic is the 5th level spell Creation?",
        "answers": [
            "Illusion",
            "Conjuration",
            "Transmutation",
            "Abjuration"
        ],
        "correct": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "In Vecna Lives, who of these mages was killed?",
        "answers": [
            "Bigby",
            "Mordenkainen",
            "Leomund",
            "Tasha"
        ],
        "correct": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "In 5th edition, how many attacks can a 20th level fighter make while they use 2 weapons, are hasted and use action surge.",
        "answers": [
            "9",
            "10",
            "11",
            "12"
        ],
        "correct": 2
    },
    {
        "question": "In the Dungeons & Dragons movie, the heroes must run from a dragon, what is the name of this dragon?",
        "answers": [
            "Themberchaud",
            "Umbralax",
            "Razorfang",
            "Arngalor"
        ],
        "correct": 1
    }
]